

#### CONTACT ME AT

- Johor Bahru, Malaysia
- +60 196792120
- hw.siew.work@gmail.com
- https://github.com/hwsiew
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/hw-siew/
- https://stackoverflow.com/users/5150558/hw-siew

#### SKILLS SUMMARY

- •••• Javascript
- •••• ReactJs
- •••• ExpressJs
- •••• NodeJs
- •••• MongoDB
- •••• Docker
- •••• LINUX
- •••• Python
- •••• Django
- •••• Git
- •••• Typescript
- • • WordPress Development

# CERTIFICATION

Google IT Automation with Python Specialization by Coursera (T4QKF23F4Y8D)

# HONG WEI, SIEW

## FULL STACK WEB ENGINEER

## PERSONAL PROFILE

I am an experienced Full Stack Web Engineer with holistic knowledge of software development and design. Since 2015, I have participated in various small and mid-scale web developments. I am familiar with a number of programming languages, frameworks, and tools such as MERN stack, VueJs, Typescript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Docker, Git, Webpack, WordPress, Python, Django, Nginx, and Linux server configuration using GCP and AWS.

I have also experience in algorithm design with proven track records and publications. I am a self-motivated and self-taught professional who likes to solve problems.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Research Engineer

Multimedia University | Jan 2019 - present

- Collaborated with the largest ISP in Malaysia
- Design and develop algorithms for network migration
- Integrate the proposed algorithms into next-gen network operation and monitoring systems.
- 1 patent had been filed

## Full Stack Web Engineer

Treazpass Advertising Sdn Bhd | Jan 2017 - Dec 2018

- End-to-end web application development as per client requirement
- Completed and successfully launched a number of midscale projects using various technology stacks.

# Full Stack Web Engineer

Thesigner | Sept 2015 - Dec 2016

- A startup to develop an online marketplace for fashion designer
- Responsible for all aspects of product development from design, development to deployment over public cloud.

#### **EDUCATIONAL HISTORY**

#### Multimedia University

Masters of Science | March 2013 - July 2015

- Major in Information Technology
- The thesis involved studying security vulnerability in All-Optical Network and proposed various algorithms to detect the location(s) of attack.

#### Multimedia University

Bachelor of Computer Science | Jun 2009 - Nov 2012

• First Class Honors with CGPA: 3.91/4